بالصلاة
تطيب لي الحياة
وأرضي بها الإله
يحلو الوصال
راحتي
إن ضاقت كربتي
توجهت لقبلتي
قم يا بـلال
فالأذان
يُشعرني الأمـان
والصـلاة
تعيـد لي الحيـاة
I see Your light
five times everyday
melting my fears away
Oh when I pray
I hear the call
it led me to Your door
I want my heart to soar
to You my Lord
Oh God above
bless me with Your love
and keep me true
loving and praising You
للإلـه
سعيت إلى الصلاة
منـاجاةً نجـاة
فـله المـآل
عزّتي
بركوعي وسجدتي
بها حريتي
لك ذا الجـلال
فالأذان
يشعرني الأمـان
والصـلاة
تعـيد لي الحيـاة
When I'm sad
and wipe away a tear
I know You're always near
my pain You hear
Oh I was lost
and no one was with me
I was blind but now I see
by Your mercy
Oh God above
bless me with Your love
and keep me true
loving and praising You
تعيــد لي الحيــاة